1991年  越南岘港
人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
翻译    CapitalJack  Amy  四畹饭
翻译    Caroline  三四月  DerbyNinja
时间轴    无关风粤  噃噃bobo   今  壬虚浪影
你好  外面这些都是你干的吗
Hello, did you do all of this?
后期    吉吉
校对    小酸奶
总监    小酸奶
贝瑞塔93手枪
Beretta 93.
通常还是很好用的
Usually dependable.
现在应该没问题了
We should be good to go now.
来啊
Come on.
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
三十年后
罗马尼亚  布加勒斯特
什么情况  你们在开派对吗
What the fuck? Are you having a party?
安东在哪
Where is Anton?
他为什么不接电话
Why didn't he answer the phone?
瓦利
Vali!
你爸在找你
Your father is looking for you.
起床
Get up!
快起来  瓦利
Get up, Vali!
快点  姑娘们  快回家去
Come on, girls, come on. Go home.
快走  快走  快点  快出去
Away, away! Come on, get out of here.
快点  瓦利  我们走吧
Come on Vali, let's go.
安东
Anton?
瓦利他妈的在哪
Where the fuck is Vali?
你应该照顾好他  瓦利到底在哪
You had to look over him, where the fuck is Vali?
你好
Yes?
你是谁
Who's talking?
是我  瓦利
It's me, Vali.
瓦利
Vali?
告诉我你都去哪了  你为什么不
Explain to me where did you go? Why don't you...
几个混蛋把我从酒店里绑了出来
Some assholes kidnapped me outside the hotel.
什么  是谁
What? Who?
是谁绑架了你
Who kidnapped you?
我他妈怎么会知道
How the fuck would I know?
他们现在想要三百万欧元
They want three million euros now.
瓦利  告诉他们我是什么人
Vali, tell them how I am.
他们才不在乎你是谁  快交赎金
They don't fucking care who you are, just pay!
他们在两个小时内要拿到三百万欧元
They want three million euros in two hours.
不然他们会像杀猪一样宰了我
Or they'll cut my throat like a pig.
你怎么敢绑架我儿子
How dare you take my boy?
钱在那  你想点点吗
There it is. You wanna count it?
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
唐·普雷达
Don Preda.
布加勒斯特屠夫  杀人狂魔
Butcher of Bucharest, Killer of Men.
告诉你老板钱已经收到了
Tell your boss it's done.
你们到底是什么人
Exactly, who are you people?
我们只是
We're just...
我们能找到那些找不到的人而已
We just find people who can't be found.
那些钱
The money.
你可以大概拥有它们一个小时
You gonna have it maybe for an hour.
然后我们会拿回来
Then we come take it back,
再把你们砍成碎块  喂给我的猪
cut you both into pieces and feed you to my pigs.
你不害怕吗
That doesn't worry you?
不
No.
为什么
Why?
我来这不是为了拿钱
I didn't come here for money.
是为了你
I came here for you.
拦下那女的  她杀了唐·普雷达  杀了她
Stop the girl. She killed Don Preda. Kill her.
你干吗这么使劲挣扎
Why are you fighting so hard, huh?
王八蛋  你要回家了  滚开
You're going home, motherfucker. Fuck off!
我很好
I'm good.
你们两个王八蛋  你们不能把我留在这
You fucking pieces of shit. You can't leave me here!
去死吧  混蛋
Fuck you, you bastards!
你有没有带点出来
Did you take any, huh?
带什么
Take what?
钱
Money.
赎金都准备好了的吧
It was all there, right?
我们收钱杀目标  其他的不管
We were paid to eliminate the target. We did that.
没错  可你知道三百万的赃款  也没人知道
Yeah, you know, three mil... dirty money... nobody's looking for...
我就随口一说
Just saying.
抱歉  我不知道你这么敏感
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't know you're hurting.
得了吧
Please.
我是R&D管道修理公司的  你的问题已经解决了
This is R & D Plumbing. Your leak has been fixed.
请完成余款的缴付
Please remit the balance of your payment for the withd...
七百万欧元转账成功
搞定
Done.
你得去看看你的咳嗽了
You need to see a doctor about that cough.
看普通医生还是巫婆
Traditional or a witch?
你去看  肯定得去找巫婆了
You? Definitely a witch.
我正好知道一位合适的巫后
I know just the voodoo queen to call.
伦敦
书店
新书  二手书
切姆斯福德真是个糟透的战争区
Chelmsford was a bloody war zone.
每班火车都晚点三十分钟  路上永远在堵车
Every train was 30 minutes late and jam-packed as always.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
谢谢你照顾她
Thank you for taking care of her,
你应该知道你是她唯一能忍受的人  对吧
you know you're the only one she'll tolerate, right?
你走了以后她变得好凶
She gets really mean when you're away.
大部分时间都和普鲁斯特一起玩
Spent most of the time hanging out with Proust.
是真的吗
Is that true?
走了三周  你就带回了这个
Three weeks, and this is all you come back with?
你知道那些卖家的
Ah, you know sellers,
他们知道你千里迢迢过去  就开始扮高冷
they know you've come all that way, and they play hard to get.
真想弄死那种人啊
Didn't you wanna just kill people like that?
你想干什么呀
What do you think you're doing, huh?
有一天他跟我说"七十岁是新的三十岁"
So, the other day, he says to me "70 is the new 30."
老人家可能都会这么想吧
Well, that's just something old guys say.
他治疗得怎么样了
How is he doing with his protocol?
他有没有听医生的嘱咐
Is he following the doctor's orders?
这么说吧  他更喜欢听自己的嘱咐
More like, following his own orders.
生日快
Happy birth...
我不想再过狗屁生日了
No more fucking birthdays.
拿走我的生日  堵上你们的屁眼
Take birthdays and shove them up your ass.
混蛋
Bastard.
这玩具可太棒了
What a wonderful toy!
看来你节省了不少蜡烛啊
You skimped on the candles I see.
点七十根蜡烛就该起火灾了
Seventy would have been a fire hazard.
能麻烦你给我们准备些茶吗
Could you make us some tea please?
没问题
Sure.
好了  许愿吧
All right, make your wish.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
谢了
Yeah.
感谢你的礼物
To thank you.
1958年吉普森的翱翔者五号
A 1958 Gibson Flying V.
这种琴只出产了两年
This was in production just two years.
现在全世界也只有九十把
There is only 90 in the whole world.
我知道
I know.
这音色
That sound...
来源于琴身的木料
It's the wood.
用的是非洲的榄仁树
African limba.
没有其它材质可以有这种音色
Nothing else sounds like it.
我本来都要放弃寻找这把琴了
I was just about giving up hope on finding one.
你到底是怎么找
How in the world did you...
因为你
You.
是你教授我如何找到不想被找到的东西的
You taught me how to find things that didn't wanna be found.
艾伯特·金弹过一把
Albert King played one.
艾伯特·金弹过的就是这把
Albert King played that one.
不是吧
No!
你都快哭了  对不对
You're gonna cry now, aren't you?
那也只是因为我的琴技辜负了这把琴
Only because I can't play it the way it needs to be played.
谢谢你
Thank you.
昨晚双胞胎中的一个打给我  说她怀孕了
One of the twins called me last night, said she was pregnant.
住在多佛的黛西
Daisy in Dover?
不  是住在曼彻斯特的黛西
No, Daisy in Manchester.
住在多佛的黛西是同性恋
Daisy in Dover is a dyke.
能够拥有一个足够相信你  除非你寻求帮助
It is a rare gift to have a friend who trusts you enough
否则不会试着帮助自己的朋友是非常幸运的事
not to try and help until you ask.
带这么多东西掉进池塘里你就沉底了
If you fell in the pond with those you'd drown.
要是我掉进池塘里没带着这些
Well, if I fell in a pond without them
可能就漂走了
I would probably float away.
-你好  小可爱  -小心手指
- Hi, honey. - Mind your fingers.
那小家伙可会咬人
That hefa bites.
她还小  都不懂事
She's a baby and doesn't know any better.
来吧
There.
你有自己的秘密基地
You have your own secret hideout.
我真是一点都不意外
Why am I not surprised?
我买下了那栋楼
I bought the building.
-什么楼  -那家书店
- What? - The bookstore.
现在是你的了  随你处置
It's yours. Free and clear.
你没必要那么做的
You didn't have to do that.
我知道  但那是你的激情所在
I know, but it's your passion.
而且知道我不在以后
And, it makes me feel good to know
你有事可忙  我就放心了
you'll have something to work on while I'm gone.
那是什么
What is that?
那些是在另一边等待我的鬼魂们
Those are the souls waiting for me on the other side.
我相信他们已经在筹备我的欢迎会了
I'm sure they have a reception planned.
这么多人都英年早逝了
Ah... sent away so many prematurely.
不是我杀的  就是你杀的
Either by my hand or through you.
我们杀的都是罪有应得的人
We never sent anyone away who didn't have it coming.
也许吧
Maybe.
但是...  我相信上面肯定有不少人
But... I'm sure there are quite a few spirits up there
等着找我的茬呢
waiting for me with a bone to pick.
你真的相信你会上天堂
You really believe you're going up?
你不是吗
Don't you?
卢卡斯·海耶斯
Lucas Hayes.
我需要我们的朋友帮忙找到他
I need our friend to find him for me.
1998年还有他的消息  在巴黎  那以后杳无音讯
I have him up till 1998, Paris, after that nothing.
-找到就行  -找到就行
- Just find? - Just find.
低调  但是得迅速
Discreetly, and with the quickness.
好吧
Okay.
我可能得回一趟越南
I may have to go back to Vietnam.
你要是能陪我回去就好了
It'd be nice if you went with me.
我再也不想回去了
I'm never going back there.
我们的过去会一直伴随着我们  小变色龙
Our past is never where we left it, little chameleon.
我们都有旧伤疤
We all have scars.
你看见他们  就会想起往事
You stare at them long enough you remember how you got them.
早上好
Hi. Morning.
蓝裙子上面撕破了一小块
The blue dress has a small tear in it,
我能不能跟本尼说一下
I was hoping to talk to Benny about it.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
什么怎么样
Of what?
我的胡子
My, mustache.
我今天没戴隐形眼镜  不好意思
Oh, you know, I don't have my contacts in, sorry.
真逗
Funny.
你等他们长长一点  你们这样的女人就会
You wait till this grows in women like you are gonna be so...
不  没关系  我会帮你的
No, it's okay. I'll help you out.
我需要你帮我找到这个人
I need you to find this guy.
什么  不是布加勒斯特郊区黑手党老巢的照片吗
What? No satellite shots of a mafia compound outside Bucharest?
不是  但是那一票你干得不错
No, but that was some of your better work.
穆迪想找这个人  卢卡斯·海耶斯
Moody wants this guy, Lucas Hayes,
最近一次露面是98年的时候在巴黎
last seen in Paris in '98 and then nothing.
我马上就来帮你
I'll be with you in a second.
需要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
我在找一本书  一本旧书  算是挺稀有
Yeah, I'm looking for a book, an old book. Like, rare.
算是挺稀有
"Like rare"?
他们要么是稀有的  要么是不稀有的
Either they are or they aren't.
书不是大熊猫  不是你想稀有就稀有的
Books aren't like stake, you can't get them like medium rare.
-有意思  -这是讽刺
- It's funny. - Sarcastic.
我知道  但是有意思
Yes, but funny.
我老板的太太要开派对
Listen, my boss' wife is having a party
她爱好收集书  第一版的那种
and she collects books, first editions.
-有类别偏好吗  -鸟类  奥多本的...
- Any particular subject? - Birds. It's Audobon's...
-《美洲鸟类》 -对  就是那个
- "Birds of America"? - Yeah, that's it.
他说她在找某一个版本
He said she's looking for a copy.
第一版的
A first edition?
-抱歉  -你们没有吗
- Sorry. - You don't have it?
没人有  现存的唯一一本
No one does, only one first editions exists,
1991年以960万的价格卖给了一位私人买家
it was sold to a private buyer in 1991 for a 9.6 million dollars.
好吧
Wow, okay.
看来我运气不太好
Well, looks like I'm out of luck.
好吧  你觉得什么适合  诗集行不行
All right. What do you think? Maybe poetry?
等一下...
Hang on...
它会成为派对上的热点
It'll be the hit of the party.
《塔默兰诗集》
我...  我没听说过这本
I don't... I don't know this one.
作者其实是埃德加·爱伦·坡
It's Edgar Allan Poe actually.
他的第一本诗集  匿名发表的
His first collection of poems published anonymously.
你觉得她会不会已经有了
You think she might have it?
应该不会  它只印刷了50本
Doubtful. Only 50 copies were printed.
存世的只有12本
Only 12 are known to exist.
多少钱
How much?
我可以二十六万五卖给你
I can give it to you for $265,000.
要不你还是买个镯子吧
Perhaps a bracelet instead?
她的手腕确实很美  好主意
She does have exquisite wrists, good idea.
还有别的事吗
Is there something else?
我觉得你有意思
I find you interesting.
-你的意思是...  -你很有意思
- You mean... - You're interesting.
很美  当然  但不只是外表美丽那种
Beautiful, sure, not in that ornamental kind of way.
就是这个有意思的部分让我好奇
It's the interesting part that got me wondering.
好奇什么
Wondering what?
好奇我把手机号给你以后你需要花多长时间
How long after I give you my number will it take you
来决定我也一样的有意思然后给我打电话
to decide that I'm just as interesting and give me a call?
二十七分钟
Twenty seven minutes.
那么久吗
That long?
首先我得假装取消我原先的约会
First I have to pretend to cancel my date
然后我还得喂猫
and then I have to feed my cat.
六分钟够了
That's six.
其余的时间就是欲擒故纵了
The rest is me playing hard to get.
可爱
Cute.
你随身携带多少这种卡片  伦...
How many of these are you carrying around, Mr...
伦勃朗  迈克尔·伦勃朗
Rembrandt. Michael Rembrandt.
其实我在今天之前还一直没机会用
Actually, I haven't had an occasion to use one until just now.
所以...
So...
有意思
Interesting.
"这里曾伫立着一座喷泉
"There rose a fountain once,
美丽花朵在它周围开放"
and there full many a fair flower raised its head."
是那本书里的诗句  对吧
That was from the book, wasn't it.
"但照料他们的女士早已仙逝
"But she who rear'd them was long dead,
与尘世俗务再无关联"
And in such follies had no part."
这次差点让你骗到了
You almost got me on this one.
你可没提过让我追查的这个人才八岁
You didn't say I'd be tracking an eight year old.
卢卡斯·海耶斯确实98年的时候来过巴黎
Lucas Hayes did arrive in Paris in '98,
但是99年3月回岘港了
but returned to Da Nang, March '99.
我找到的其余信息都在这里面了
Everything else I have is on there.
B·B·金  乡村大门现场
准备就绪
本尼
Benny?
你在那里等着我过去  45分钟
You'll stay up until I get there, 45 minutes.
出生证明
卢卡斯·海耶斯  1990年4月5日出生
父亲  爱德华·海耶斯
母亲  玛丽·克里斯蒂安
护照申请表
卢卡斯·海耶斯
圣奎特丽娅医院
卢卡斯·海耶斯于1999年6月2日入住圣奎特丽娅医院
父亲  爱德华·海耶斯  于1991年圣诞节被暗杀
无其他记录
生于恶兆
爱德华·亚瑟·海耶斯
因战争罪被起诉的商人死于汽车炸弹袭击
爱德华·海耶斯... 昨日于岘港死于汽车爆炸
穆迪
Moody.
CEO保证  "公司会继续运作"
"爱德华·海耶斯和我已经搭档了25年了"  沃尔说  "我会继续继承他的遗志带领公司前行"
约西诺·沃尔
越南  岘港
操  搞什么
Shit! What the fuck is that?
妈的
Fuck.
宝贝  过来
Honey! Come on.
没想到我会在这里再见到你
Never thought I'd see you here again.
也许你见到的不是我
Well, maybe you're not seeing me now.
哪来的婊子
Who's the bitch?
比利小子...
Billy Boy...
我知道你什么人都可以合作  但是现在跟傻子一起工作了吗
I know you run with all kinds but now you're running with stupid?
去你妈的
Fuck you!
去喝点东西  宝贝
Hey! Go get a drink, sugar,
给大人们一点隐私空间
and give the adults some privacy, huh?
啤酒
Beers!
外面是你的车吗
Is that your ride outside?
现在是你的了
Yours now.
今天不是我生日
It ain't my birthday.
约西诺·沃尔
穆迪怎么样了
How's Moody?
他死了
He's dead.
敬穆迪
For Moody.
跟沃尔有关吗
Vohl involved?
我不知道  但他知道是谁干的
I don't know. But he knows who is.
-这个人不太好杀  -我只想跟他聊聊
- He's gonna be hard to kill. - I just wanna talk to him.
斯蒂维里诺
Steverino!
怎么了  头儿
Yeah, Boss?
你在国家大厦当保安
You work security at the State Tower.
我朋友想跟沃尔聊两句
My friend there needs a few minutes with Vohl.
单独的
Alone.
你想都别想
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
他到哪儿都有私人保镖跟着
He goes nowhere without private security.
这家伙永远不会孤身一人
The guy's never alone.
沃尔控股有限公司
出什么事了
What is happening?
我要找到您就是这么容易  沃尔先生
This is how easy it is for me to get to you, Mr. Vohl.
明白了吗
Do you understand?
您曾经是爱德华·海耶斯的朋友兼生意伙伴
You were friends and business partners with Edward Hayes,
所以您是对他有趣而短暂的一生了解最多的人
so you would know most about his short but interesting life.
很好  我有问题要问您
Good, cause I have questions.
您告诉我答案  如果我满意  您就再也不用见我
You give me answers: if I'm satisfied you'll never see me again,
如果我不满意  我就是您最后见到的人
if I'm not, I'll be the last thing you'll ever see.
那我就静候佳音了
I look forward to hearing from you.
晚上好  女士
Good evening, Miss.
距离上次一位年轻美女
It's been a long time since such
给我留电话已经很久了
a beautiful young woman gave me her number.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
约西诺·沃尔  出生于1945年4月
Jossino Vohl, born in April, 1945.
法国人  现居越南
French national, residing full time in Vietnam.
一直和爱德华·海耶斯有生意往来
Was in business with Edward Hayes
直到他英年早逝
until his untimely death.
现在你是一名顶级政治掮客
Now you're a top political power broker
还有一些有趣的业余爱好
with some interesting side hobbies.
看来你对我的履历很熟悉啊
I see you're familiar with my resume.
我对您的商业活动毫无兴趣  沃尔先生
I am not interested in your business activities, Mr. Vohl.
我想跟您谈谈您朋友的儿子卢卡斯
I want to talk about your friend's son, Lucas.
一小时后我的办公室见
My office, one hour.
就我们俩吗
We'll be alone?
我的律师会在场
My lawyer will be present.
是站在你身后倒威士忌的那个人吗
That would be the man standing behind you pouring a scotch?
幸会  女士
Delighted, Miss.
时间刚刚好
Exactly on time.
请
Please.
杜奎特先生  我的私人律师
Monsieur Duquet, my personal attorney.
-你要来点香槟吗  -爱德华·亚瑟·海耶斯
- Would you like some champagne? - Edward Arthur Hayes.
艾迪在出意外前和我一起参与了一个
Eddie and I were involved in a bauxite mining project together
铝土矿开采项目
until his accident.
那不是意外  是暗杀
It wasn't an accident, it was an assassination.
我们做了很多有益的事
We were useful.
这个国家可塑性很强  适合某些商业实践
The country was malleable, ripe for certain business practices.
艾迪那时一个人同时兼顾了很多项目
Eddie was juggling a lot of delicate plates.
你对一个死了快三十年的人
What's your interest in a man
好奇些什么
who's been dead almost thirty years?
我对他儿子感兴趣
I'm interested in his son.
卢卡斯·海耶斯
Lucas Hayes.
什么意思
I'm sorry?
有三个人因调查他而死
Three people are dead because they inquired about him.
他害死了他们  我要找到他
He had them killed and I'm going to find him.
我应该和他聊吗
Should I be talking to him?
我跟卢卡斯·海耶斯没有联系
I have no connection with Lucas Hayes.
这跟我有什么关系
And what does any of this got to do with me?
我也正想知道
I was wondering the same thing.
沃尔先生生前的人际关系与我们无关
Mr. Vohl's past relationships are no one's concern.
当然跟你们也没关系
And certainly none of yours.
但跟我有关
Oh, I've made them my concern.
可惜
Too bad.
我要知道所有事情
I need to know everything.
你是谁
Who are you?
谁雇的你
Who hired you?
为什么要打听卢卡斯·海耶斯
Why the interest in Lucas Hayes?
如果你愿意我  们可以换个方式
We can do this another way if you'd like.
妈的  放开我
Fucking let me go!
爬上去
Get up there.
给我把枪
Hand me a gun.
洒水阀
Sprinkler valve
你他妈要上哪儿去
Where the fuck do you think you're going?
让他们放下枪
Say it.
-去你妈的  -快说
- Fuck you! - Say it!
她在下面
She's down there!
先说说你叫什么吧
Let's start with your name.
穆迪找爱德华·海耶斯的儿子做什么
Why was Moody looking for Edward Hayes' son?
还有谁跟这件事有关
Who else out there should we know about?
妈的
Fuck!
从没人能撑这么久
Anyone ever last this long.
这已经超出我们掌控了
It's out of our hands now, anyway.
他要来
Him?
那个27分钟可真够长的
That was a long 27 minutes.
我还在等你电话呢
I'm still waiting for your call.
没关系
It's all right.
我不会公私不分的
I don't take these things personally.
骨头汤
Bone broth.
有助于消炎和治疗瘀伤
Helps with inflammation and bruising.
来
Here.
小心点  很烫
Careful. It's hot. Watch it.
很好
There you go.
我个人很喜欢
I like this myself.
来  小口喝
Here you go, small sips.
还好吗
Good?
实话跟你说
Not gonna lie to you,
硬撑下去对你没好处
there's not much of a chance this ends well for you.
外面那个人
That guy out there.
跟我一样都是为同一个人工作
We work for the same individual.
老板有麻烦了就打给他  他负责解决
Boss has a problem. He calls him, he takes care of it.
他们的解决方式很粗暴  但这由不得我决定
Little heavy handed for my taste but that's not my call.
你朋友穆迪的死  我很遗憾
I'm sorry about your friend, Moody.
我没参与那件事
I had no part in that.
书店放火也与我无关
Or the fire fight at the bookstore.
我就是个善后的
I'm an after-the-facts guy.
我负责扫尾工作
I come in to make sure there's no loose ends.
我负责找出那些看似正常的事物背后的东西
I look for things that might seem benign, but aren't.
就像是杀手经营的书店
Like a bookstore run by an assassin,
天  我还是真没想到
boy, I never saw that one coming.
我完全误读了你
I misread you completely.
我可以帮你出去
I can help you out of here.
好吗
Okay?
但你也得帮我
But you have to help me.
我是你最后一根救命稻草
I'm your last line of defense.
你已经山穷水尽  无路可走了
End of the road, no more lifelines.
听明白了吗
You understand?
好了
All right.
你忘了烫骨头
You forgot to blanch the bones.
你的汤
Your soup.
你在烤骨头之前必须先把它焯一下
You have to blanch the bones before you roast them.
帮助锁住矿物质  对治疗更有好处
Locks the minerals in, it's better for healing.
你套出什么话了吗
You got anything out of her?
有  也没有
Yes and no.
你这话他妈的什么意思
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
意思是我明早会回来跟进她的情况
Means I'll be back in the morning to follow up with her.
-我这儿用不着你  伦勃朗  -是吗
- I don't need you here, Rembrandt. - Well...
我们的金主可不这么想
The man who signs the checks thought differently.
-是吗  -没错
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
为什么
And why is that?
我也不知道
Oh, I don't know.
可能是因为你没经过他同意就杀了沃尔吧
Maybe it's because you killed Vohl without asking his permission.
沃尔什么都知道  他是直接关系人
Vohl knew everything, he was a direct connection.
他一倒就全完了
Would've folded like a tent.
是啊  笑死我了  你们都一样
You... yes, kill me, you're all the same:
先开枪  后提问
Shoot first and ask questions later.
先别用你们那些强化审讯技巧
And hold off on those enhanced interrogation techniques.
我要她明天早上头脑清醒
I want her clear-headed in the morning.
他明天会突破她的
He'll break her tomorrow.
或许他已经突破了
Maybe he broke her already.
老爷子已经迫不及待要知道她知道的信息
The old man is desperate to know what she knows.
我想知道如果他的神奇小子
I wonder how it'd feel if his boy wonder
在他发现之前杀了她会是什么感觉
ends up killing her before he finds out.
我猜他会找个新的神奇小子了
I'm guessing he'll look for a new boy wonder.
我们才刚开始互相了解呢
Just when we were getting to know each other.
机场  船厂和火车站都安排了人
I've got teams at the airport, shipyard and train station.
她不会跑远  她只会找个地方养伤
She's not gonna run, she's gonna lick her wounds.
然后回来追杀你
Then she's coming after you.
很好
Good.
是吗
Really?
但现在是4比0了  她领先
Cause right now it's 4:0. She's wining.
你这西服哪里买的
Where do you buy your suits?
我有个表亲跟你差不多块头
Cause I've got a cousin as big and tall
他的就很难做
and he's a hard time.
呆子
Nobody's home.
我能把你送到边境去
Well, I can get you to the border.
现在伦敦对你来说不安全
London may not be safe for you right now.
这里是越南  安娜
This is Vietnam, Anna,
你知道这里是什么样的
you know what's it like here.
好好活着  这是你欠穆迪的
You owe it to Moody to stay alive.
我知道我欠了他什么
I know what I owe him.
走吧
Go.
你他妈以为我给你钱是为了...
The fuck you think I gave you the money of...
到此为止了  孩子
End of the line, kid.
进去
Get in!
小心
Watch out!
穆迪很美  以他独特的方式
Moody was beautiful, in his way.
他很善良
He was kind.
不是后天努力  而是他与生俱来的一部分
And not through effort, it was just a part of who he was.
他不是救了我一命  而是给了我一命
He didn't save my life, he gave me a life.
他知道我是谁  我是个什么样的人
He knew who I was, what I've become.
但他还是保护了我
And he protected me.
海耶斯已经死了30年了
Hayes has been dead for thirty years,
沃尔离开得更早
Vohl was gone longer.
有一群罪大恶极的人正在找你
You've got some very bad people looking for you.
卢卡斯·海耶斯杀了穆迪
Lucas Hayes killed Moody,
他知道我在找他
he knows I'm looking for him.
他最后出现的地方是圣奎特丽娅医院
His last known location is St. Quiteria Hospital.
你永远叫不醒一个装聋的人
Nobody is as deaf as those who don't wanna listen.
你好  阮女士
Hello, Ms. Nguyen.
我们已经有一段时间
It's been some time since
没有接待过卫生部的来访了
we've had a visit from the Ministry of Health.
还是来调取那么久远的记录...
And to request records from that far back...
是的  我明白
Yes, I know.
我们希望能从中找到一些
We're hoping to find something in there
能帮我们排除环境因素的线索
that will help us rule out environmental factors,
因为我们正在进行一项研究
cause we are in the midst of a study.
谢谢
Thank you.
卢卡斯·海耶斯  我来之前就在这里了
Lucas Hayes, well before my time here.
编号2585024586
2585024586.
收到  我让医生去查
Copy, I'll get Doc on it.
好的
Okay.
医生来过了  调出了他的记录
Doc came through, pulled his records.
然后呢
And?
听好了  卢卡斯·海耶斯在1999年
Sit down: Lucas Hayes was admitted to
6月2日被收入圣奎特丽娅医院
St. Quiteria on 2nd June, 1999,
根据他的记录显示  他再没离开过
and according to his records never left.
我很抱歉  看来这个男孩
I apologize, seems the boy
是以克里斯蒂安这个名字重新收入的
was re-admitted under the name Christian.
克里斯蒂安  没错  他母亲婚前的姓氏
Christian, right, his mother's maiden name.
我来的时候他已经在这里了
He was already here when I arrived,
作为病人待了超过20年
been a patient for more than twenty years.
他不喜欢被人碰触
He doesn't like to be touched.
他没法说话  还又聋又盲
He can't speak. Also deaf and blind.
他这样多久了
And how long has he been like this?
他大概六岁时被确诊
He was diagnosed when he was six, I believe,
然后病情快速恶化
it regressed rapidly.
他能活这么久都是个奇迹
It's a miracle he's lived as long.
他的医疗费由谁支付
And who pays for his care?
我们的善款充裕
We have a generous endowment.
这里的每个人都接受免费的治疗
Everyone here is treated for free.
四个人死了  监控却什么也没拍到
Four men dead, nothing on camera.
那地方看起来像个屠宰场
Place looks like an abattoir.
是因为食物吗
Was it the food?
你知道  他们很没礼貌
You know, it was bad manners.
这样对待淑女可不好
Yeah, well, that's no way to treat a lady.
我不是淑女
I'm no lady.
我也不是什么绅士
Not that I was a gentleman myself.
我可不会这样贬低自己
I wouldn't sell yourself short.
从你嘴里说出来的话  这就是赞美
Coming from you, that's a compliment.
我正在办一些事...
I'm in the middle of something...
圣奎特丽娅修女还好吗
Hey, how were good sisters of the St. Quiteria?
好到足以让我知道
Good enough to let me know
我找错人了
I've been looking for the wrong person.
真是些好姑娘
Good gals out there.
圣奎特丽娅  你知道她是谁吗
St. Quiteria, do you know who she was?
她15岁的时候
Fifteen years old,
领导了一场对抗罗马军团的游击战
she led a guerrilla war against the Roman legions.
不简单
Bad ass.
他们砍掉了她的头  剩下的喂了狗
They chopped off her head and fed the rest to the dogs.
又是这么不礼貌
Again, bad manners.
你想吃晚饭吗
Hey, you up for a dinner?
我可以回答几个问题  帮你节省点时间
I could answer some questions and save you some time.
拉塞克餐厅怎么样  明晚八点
What do say if we say La Cinq? Tomorrow night, eight o'clock.
你可以提议  但我不会去的
I mean you can say it. But I won't be there.
我会告诉你时间和地点
I'll give you the time and place.
你被她迷住了
You're intrigued by her.
好奇而已
Curious.
我需要担心吗
Need I worry?
晚会名单  先生  200名宾客都审查过了
The gala list, sir, 200 guests, all vetted.
满屋权贵以为崇高事业
The joys of a room full of the wealthy and the privileged
一掷千金为乐
donating large sums for a noble cause.
永不过时
Never gets old.
很好
Good.
你为什么这么做
Why did you do this?
在其位  谋其事  迈克尔
It's what people in my position are supposed to do, Michael.
向不幸的人施以援手
Give to the less fortunate.
我问我是不是该担心
I asked if I should be worried.
关于那个女人
About the woman.
不用  还不是时候
Nope. Not yet.
请在周日前解决这件不愉快的事
Please wrap up this unpleasantness by Sunday.
我不想在庆祝典礼前尴尬
I don't wanna be embarrassed before the celebration.
谢谢你  本
Thank you, Ben.
他们都认识我
They know me here.
干杯
Cheers.
有人因为我朋友在几年前
Someone killed a friend of mine
完成的一项委托而杀死了他
because of a contract he completed years ago.
我询问过的所有人最后都死了
And anyone I ask about it ends up dead.
为什么会这样
Why is that?
我不知道  但有人会认为这是个信号
I don't know, but some people might take it as a sign.
你为什么不把它当做一个最好别解开的谜题呢
Why don't you just consider it a mystery best left unsolved?
但我喜欢谜题
But I like mysteries.
当我开始调查的时候  我很好奇
When I started this I was curios.
然后我从好奇变成了担心
And then I went from curious to concerned.
现在呢
And now?
我很暴躁
I'm testy.
相信我  你不会想认识暴躁的我
An trust me, you don't wanna know me when I'm testy.
HK9毫米
HK 9mm.
非常好
Very good.
在我看来不是
Not from where I'm sitting.
谁在为那个孤儿买单
Who's paying for the orphan kid?
我想和那个人谈谈
I'd like to talk to whoever that is.
那可不明智
That'd be unwise.
杀害如同我父亲一样的人  才是不明智的
Unwise is killing a man who was a second father to me.
我们已经过了讨论明智的阶段
We are way past unwise.
这里真的不适合杀人
This is a really bad place for a hit.
高档餐厅  每个出口都有保安
High-end restaurant, the security at every exit,
更别说监控了
not to mention the cameras.
看来你都很清楚了
You know what, you already knew that.
我可不是来杀你的...
Oh, I'm not here to kill you...
目前来说  只是想要答案
Yet. Just to get answers.
你总是这样有求于人吗
You always ask like this?
是啊  我说话的时候喜欢引起别人的注意
Yeah, I like to have peoples' attention when I talk, you know?
好吧...
Well...
你成功引起了下面那群伙计的注意
you certainly have the attention of the boys down there.
听着  以防万一你至少得打我三枪
Look, you're gonna have to put at least three in me to be sure.
四枪
Four.
好吧  那你就只剩五颗子弹了  就算有麻烦
Fine. That leaves you with five. In case there's trouble.
你觉得这样你就能从这里逃出去了吗
You think that's enough to get you out of here?
是啊  只需要快速开四枪
Four quick shots and then the slow walk
然后趁着混乱慢慢走向出口
to the exit amongst the chaos. Yeah.
总有意料之外的事情发生
Something unexpected could happen.
世事总是难以预料
You know, it usually does.
SIG226  后坐力非常强
SIG 226, it's got that great kick.
是啊
Yeah.
瞧瞧  我们之间第一次尴尬的沉默
How about that. Our first awkward silence.
说起来  我还不知道你的名字呢
You know what, I didn't get your name.
安娜
Anna.
-很高兴认识你  -再说吧
- Pleasure. - We'll see.
要不然我们把这些招数都忘掉
What do you say we forget these tricks.
去找一家很棒的酒店
Let's just go for a nice hotel.
你用枪指着我腿间  然后还要和我上床
You point a gun at my pussy and then you ask me to bed?
我喜欢你的风格
I like your style.
你不也是用空尖弹指着我的蛋吗
Said the woman with hollow-points pointed at my balls.
希望场面不要弄得太血腥
Well, let's hope this doesn't get messy.
这可是我最喜欢的一双鞋
These are my favorite shoes.
马诺洛牌  经典四英寸高跟鞋
Manolo's, classic four inch pumps.
懂枪又懂鞋的男人
A man who knows Poe and footwear.
让我委婉地告诉你吧
Let me put this to you delicately,
你继续下去的话会死的
you keep this up, you're gonna die.
越南一向是个死亡之地
Vietnam has always been a place of death.
只有幸运儿能活着出去  我就幸运过一次
Only lucky ones make it out alive. I was lucky once.
你不会幸运第二次的
You don't get lucky twice.
我要找出是谁杀了我的朋友
I'm going to find out who killed my friend.
找到之后呢
And when you do?
我要杀了他们
I'm going to end their life,
挡路者死
and anyone standing in my way.
谢谢你让我度过了一个愉快的夜晚
Thank you for a lovely evening.
我知道这听起来很疯狂
Hey, I know it sounds crazy,
但我真的很想再见到你
but I'd really like to see you again
当然是在不同的情况下
under, you know, different circumstances.
这次是私人时间
This was personal time.
所以这已经是你能见到我的最好情况了
So these are the best circumstances you'll ever see me in.
说
Speak.
搞定了再给我打电话
Call me when it's done.
我以为你去追查腐败的会计了
I thought you're off chasing corrupt accountants.
我找到了她的酒店房间  里面都是她的东西
I found a hotel room with all of her shit,
还有她的护照
including her passport.
名字是纳蒂亚·朱科娃
Name's Nadia Zhukova.
一个亚裔俄罗斯人
An Asian Russian.
好家伙
Boy.
真是永远看不出来
You don't really see that ever.
干得好  你肯定很累了吧
Good work, you must be exhausted, huh?
看起来我来晚了一天
Looks like I'm a day late.
还少了一美元  我都没费什么劲
And a dollar short. Didn't take much I'm afraid.
他嘴不严  是吧
He sang like a bird, didn't he?
所有的事我都知道了
All of the things I know now.
我知道你的上司是谁
I know who your boss is,
是那个人下达了杀掉穆迪的命令
the man who sanctioned Moody's killing.
他可是条大鱼
He's a big fish.
等鱼上钩的时候会更有意思
More fun when you hook him.
那么  我想
Well, then I guess...
我想我们很快就要再见面了
I guess we'll be seeing each other real soon then.
比你想象得更快
Sooner than you think.
你的手怎么了
Hey, what happened to your hand?
快点决定
Make up your mind:
杀了我  还是上了我
Kill me or fuck me?
真奇怪  我们在他的床上  而他
It's so weird that we're in this guy's bed while he's...
在那上面
up there.
挂着
You know, hanging.
不
No.
那就浪费了一张舒服的床了
Would be a waste of a nice bed.
好吧
Okay.
你做这种事多久了
How long have you been doing this?
我不是指这样
Not, you know, this, but...
时间太久  并不怀念
Long enough not to miss.
你走运了
You got lucky.
你不想杀我
You don't want me dead.
暂时不想
Yet.
你为什么没杀了我
Why haven't you killed me?
你能下手吗
Could you?
我能朝你脑后开两枪  然后去做个三明治
I could put two in the back of your head and go make a sandwich.
好吧
Well.
你总说这个事成不了
You always said this wasn't gonna work out.
确实
No.
这种事总是成不了  经验之谈
It's been my experience, it never does.
至少其他人都做不到
At least not for the other guy.
有办法解决吗
Have a way around that?
你手里握着所有的牌
You are holding all the cards.
我看着你在高空走钢丝
I'm watching a woman who walk over a shark tank
而下方就是鲨鱼池
on a tight rope in high winds.
你没办法成功  安娜
You're not gonna make it, Anna.
他是个坏人
He's a bad man.
做了很多坏事
Who's done very bad things.
你就打算这么躺着吗
So, you just gonna lay there?
孩子  很高兴见到你
Good to see you, kid.
你应该进去后就直接出来
Get in. Get out.
你只会走运一次
You know you only get lucky once.
是啊  有人刚刚也这么说
Yeah. Someone else just told me that.
好了
Okay.
老天
God!
就是一点胶水
Just a little glue.
-只是一点胶水  -你有病吧
- Just a little glue. - What's wrong with you!
没事的  咬紧牙
It's okay, grit your teeth.
天啊
Oh, God.
我还是对克劳迪娅的事感觉很难过
You know, I still feel really bad about Claudia.
她做的饭难以下咽
She couldn't cook worth a shit,
但她不该那样死去
but she didn't deserve to die like that.
-弄好了  -好了
- Here we go. - Okay.
好了  搞定了
Okay, okay. We're done here.
你真的觉得他们能那么容易杀了我吗
Did you really think they can kill me that easily?
他的脸本来就有些被打坏了
Before I blew the rest of it off
然后我又把他的脸炸毁了
he didn't have much of a face to begin with.
我留下了刚刚好
And I left just enough of me
能让当局确认我的身份的证据
for the authorities to think it was me.
很抱歉  你是第一个找到他的人
I'm sorry you had to be the one who found him.
无论什么情况  你都能随机应变
You could always think on your feet anyway.
今晚却没有
Not so much tonight.
这就是朋友该做的  对吧
That's what friends are for, right?
真好  我们又是朋友了
Good. We're friends again.
你跟人上床了  是不是
You got laid, didn't you?
我对这东西越来越依赖了
Depending more and more on this shit
不然根本没法缓解
to take the edge off.
计划是什么
So, what's the plan?
占地四百英亩  要想到那里
Four hundred acres, to get there
你得徒步穿过12英里蛇虫遍地的丛林
you'd have to hike through 12 miles of rat-infested jungle.
还不算上河流
That leaves the river,
摄像头  声波定位  巡逻艇
cameras, sonar, patrol boats.
你还是这么悲观  是不是
Still a pessimistic little shit, aren't you?
你也还是个打不死的蟑螂
And you're still a cockroach you can't kill.
我这话是褒义
I mean it in a good way.
他们知道你的到来
They know you're coming.
这是什么
What is this?
这是一个安全屋
It's a panic room,
在这个情况下就是一个安全地堡
in this case it's a panic bunker.
如果他进到这里面  你就完了
If he gets in there, you're done.
所有宾客都坐船抵达
All the guests arrive by boat,
在上岸的瞬间就会被仔细筛查
they'll be screened a moment they disembark.
周边封锁  现场安保启动
Perimeter locked down and site secured.
我还从以色列调来了
And I've added an additional team
一支16人的额外小队
of 16 out of Israel just for the night.
看起来你已经万事俱备了
Seems like you got everything covered.
迈克尔
Michael.
有什么想法吗
Thoughts?
威尼斯
Venice.
正是一年中最好的时节
It's really nice this time of year.
你应该去  现在就走
You should go. Now.
这些人完全不清楚他们将要面对什么人
These guys have no idea who they're dealing with.
收到
Copy that.
你看起来有点紧张
You look a little tense.
从王子到贩毒集团的头目  我都保护过
I've protected everyone from crowned princes to cartel kingpins.
今晚什么都不会发生
Nothing's gonna happen tonight
尤其我们还知道了她的长相
especially when we know what she looks like.
我的天
Boy...
我真的希望你提前拿到了钱
I really hope you got paid upfront.
先生
Sir.
有发现吗
Anything?
暂时没有
Nothing so far.
第一二三区都很安全
Sectors one, two and three are clear.
我正在等待第四区的报告
I'm waiting on the reports from sector four.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
非常高兴欢迎各位
It is with great pleasure that I welcome you all here
出席这个昂贵的夜晚
on this very expensive evening.
环顾整个房间  看到这么多熟悉的面孔
It warms my crusty heart to look across the room
温暖了我坚硬的心
and see so many familiar faces,
亲爱的朋友们  亲爱的商业伙伴们
dear friends, and close business associates.
还有一些不熟悉的面孔
As well as quite a few unfamiliar faces
运气好的话  很快将不复存在
that with luck will not remain so for long.
也许我甚至看到了我以前的一些敌人
Perhaps I may even have spotted a few former foes of mine.
我要特别感谢你们的到来
I want especially to thank you for coming,
感谢你们认识到自己的错误
and for seeing the error of your ways.
在这些年里
Over these considerable years,
我很满意地认识到
I've learnt to my great satisfaction
没有什么比做好事
there is no better way to cleanse the soul
为他人做出无私和善良行为
than to do good to perform selfless deeds
能更好净化心灵的方式了
and acts of kindness to sacrifice for others,
最重要的是慷慨大方
and most importantly to give generously.
因为你们的慷慨大方
It is due to your generous spirit
我们才变得富裕
that we've been able to enrich
才能改善这么多在某种程度上
and enhance the lives of so many infants, children,
急切需要照顾的幼小孩童  年轻男女的生活
young men and women in desperate need of care to a degree
没有在场的每一位
that would have been impossible
这些都是不可能实现的
to achieve without every one of you.
先生们女士们
Ladies and gentlemen,
今晚谢谢你们让我有幸成为你们的主持人
thank you for the privilege of being your host tonight.
请允许我将手伸进你们的口袋
And for allowing me to slide my hands
和包包里
into your pockets and purses,
但那是为了崇高的事业
but for a worthy a cause.
圣奎特丽娅修女出色的工作
The sisters of St. Quiteria do outstanding work... so...
发自内心的给予他人吧
give with your heart.
动态侦测
作为一个已经死了三十年的人
You look really good for a man
你的气色非常好  海耶斯先生
who's been dead thirty years, Mr. Hayes.
你是怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
密码
高科技
Technology.
总有一天会毁了我们的
It just gonna fuck us all one day.
你是什么人
Who are you?
当地球上的某个人决定你时辰将至时
I'm the big bad wolf that comes to get you
我就是那只回来抓你走的大恶狼
when someone on this Earth decides your time is up.
穆迪
Moody.
死而复生真是活受罪对吧
Resurrection is a bitch, ain't it?
你是来杀死我的  是吗
You've come to finish the job, haven't you?
多年前你的确雇过我来杀你对吧
Well, you did hire me all those years ago to kill you, right?
当时在车里的到底是谁
Who was really in that car?
重要吗  可弃之人
Does it matter? Disposable asset.
无名小卒
No one of any consequence.
我就指望像你这样的人说这种屁话
You see, that's the kind of shit I expect someone like you to say.
无名小卒
"No one of any consequence."
我这样的人
"Someone like me"?
我在道德上不可能完全正确
Man, I can't be all morally right.
我以杀人为生
I just... I kill people for a living,
提醒你一下是杀坏人  但还是一样
bad people, mind you, but still.
我从来没假装自己是好人
I never pretend to be anything else.
而你  你是众多
You, you're front and center
知名慈善事业的核心人物
of a dozen high-profile charitable causes.
世界看待你如同初雪般干净洁白
The world sees you as clean as first fucking snow.
但是你双手肮脏
But your hands are covered in shit.
满手血腥  从沙林毒气到贩卖人口
Blood, everything from sarin gas to human trafficking.
所以你知道我为什么要安排自己的死亡了吧
So you know why I had to arrange my demise.
我曾经有个儿子
I had a son,
在很多方面都表现出色
unexpected in many ways.
但是我捉摸不透我对这个孩子的爱
But what I couldn't fathom was the depths of love
有多深
I had for this child,
这个不完美  美好却脆弱孩子
this imperfect, wonderful, vulnerable boy.
如果我死了
If I were dead,
卢卡斯就不会再有任何威胁  不会受到任何伤害
Lucas would be free from any threats or harm.
屁话
Bullshit.
你也许是爱你儿子  海耶斯先生
You may love your son, Mr. Hayes,
但那是你消失的机会
but that was your chance to disappear.
你狡猾诡诈
You're very astute.
没人会去找一个死人
No one looks for a dead man.
我能继续体面的裹尸布之下继续
I was able to continue behind the shroud
这让我能够...
of respectability that allowed me to...
变成更大的恶魔
to become a bigger monster.
最讽刺的是  海耶斯先生
The irony of all of this, Mr. Hayes,
我想你弥补我对你儿子造成的过错
is that I was just trying to make amends to your son
因为我夺走了他的父亲
for taking his father away from him.
这一切都是你自找
You brought all of this on yourself.
安娜
Anna.
你的气色看起来不太好
You don't look so good.
我不知道
I don't know.
没有一杯苹果马天尼
Nothing an Apple Martini
和一升万能血解决不了的事
and a liter of AB positive won't fix?
你觉得我得到这两样东西的机率有多大
What do you think the chances are of me getting either?
微乎其微
Faint.
有什么好笑的吗
Something funny?
你认为自己没我这么坏  我就觉得很好笑
I find it amusing you think you're better than me.
不是坏
Not better.
而是不一样
Different.
这么说吧
You see,
大多数人都是好人  海耶斯先生
most people are good, Mr. Hayes.
然后偶尔会做一些明知是坏事的事
Then occasionally they do something they know is bad.
有的人就是坏人
Some people are bad,
他们每天都在努力控制自己的情绪
and they struggle every day to keep it under control.
而其他人坏到极点
Others... corrupt to the core
完全不在乎
and just don't give a damn,
我就是这种人
that would be me.
但是邪恶
But evil...
邪恶是完全不一样的生物  海耶斯先生
Evil is a completely different creature, Mr. Hayes.
邪恶之人认为作恶是可行的
Evil believes bad is okay,
而作恶的行为是正当的
its actions are justified.
脱离良心的暴力
Violence divorced from conscience,
不管代价多大  也不管对人造成的伤害多大
no matter what toll it takes or who it takes it upon.
我的朋友
And there, my friend,
那就是我们分道扬镳的地方
is where we part ways.
我只是个想为自己的罪行赎罪的坏人
I'm just a bad man who's looking to pay for his sins.
我懂了
I see.
所以你是来赎罪补偿的吗
So you are here to clear your conscience first?
你绝对不可能活着走出去
You'll never get out of here alive.
我从来没想过
I never intended to.
还有一件事
One more thing.
你本可以杀了那老家伙的
You could have killed the old man.
为什么没有开枪
Why didn't you?
计划不是杀他
That wasn't the plan.
发生了爆炸
位置
放开我
Leave me alone!
不不
No! No!
不  妈妈
No! Mom!
妈妈
Mom!
怎么这么久
What took you?
只是出来吃点东西
Just out for a bite.
你就打算一直站在那里吗
You just gonna stand there?
暂时是的
For now.
其实不必这样  安娜
It doesn't have to be this way, Anna.
再也不必这样
Not anymore.
最后我们都会为罪行付出代价的
We all have to pay for our sins eventually.
但不一定非得是今天
Doesn't have to be today.
我累了
I'm tired.
我想要安宁
I want peace.
只要你还活着  我就得不到安宁
And I can't have it while you're out there.
如果我和你说你可以呢
What if I told you you could?
是吗
Yeah?
两枪打中后脑勺
Two in the back of the head,
然后去吃个三明治
and then go have a sandwich.
你买不回过去  安娜
You can't buy back your past, Anna,
无法改变你的出身
can't change where you came from,
但你要改变你的未来
but you can change where you're going.
未来在哪
Where would that be?